<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Albany Real Estate Careers and Training Video Blog with Kevin Clancy</title>
    <description>Kevin Clancy, a top Real Estate Agent in Albany, shares his own internal real estate agent training for free. His Real Estate Training, Tips and Advice will help you sell more homes in less time.</description>
    <link>Realestatecareersinalbany.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="Realestatecareersinalbany.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 14:31:44 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 14:31:44 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.2.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>If You Want to Win in Real Estate, You Need to Be in the Arena</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/v6cyTvvMKeU?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;If you want to succeed in real estate, you need to get in the arena. Here’s what I mean by that.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“The credit belongs to the man who is actually in the arena.”&lt;/em&gt; - Theodore Roosevelt &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This quote changed my life, and I was reminded of it recently by witnessing three buyers this past week drop out of multiple-offer situations without even making an offer. These buyers really liked the homes for sale, but they didn’t want to get stuck in a bidding war. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s because of this quote that you as an agent need to ask yourself: &lt;strong&gt;Are you in real estate because it’s a hobby, or are you in the arena?&lt;/strong&gt; In other words, are you actually playing the game and getting your hands dirty every single day?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=This week, I hope you make the decision to step into the arena and make a plan that will lead you to your career goals.%20Realestatecareersinalbany.com/if-you-want-to-win-in-real-estate-you-need-to-be-in-the-arena.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“This week, I hope you make the decision to step into the arena and make a plan that will lead you to your career goals.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I started my business many years ago, there was one thought that drove me: I didn’t want to be on my deathbed wondering what would’ve happened if I tried starting a real estate business. I decided that I would rather start a business and potentially fail than regret never trying at all. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many agents out there aren’t playing for keeps. They’re not giving the business their all. They’re not in the arena. Are you taking the time every day to get better? There’s a wealth of information out there that you can use to do so. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you want to succeed in real estate, you need to get in the arena.&lt;/strong&gt; This week, I hope you make the decision to step into the arena and make a plan that will lead you to your career goals. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’d like to talk more about this topic or you have any other questions for me, feel free to reach out to me. I’d love to help you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 17:04:34 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>Realestatecareersinalbany.com/if-you-want-to-win-in-real-estate-you-need-to-be-in-the-arena.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">Realestatecareersinalbany.com/if-you-want-to-win-in-real-estate-you-need-to-be-in-the-arena.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Harness the Power of Gratitude and Watch Your Career Transform</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Fmu94b-O1K4?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Today I’ve got two incredible pieces of advice from real estate mogul Barbara Corcoran, and each of them has the power to transform your career.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While shooting my latest commercial with Barbara Corcoran, she offered me some incredible advice. To paraphrase her words of wisdom, &lt;strong&gt;“If you’re always grateful, you’ll always be successful.”&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This sentiment is one I think we should all strive to live by. It’s easy to focus on the things we don’t have, but it’s far more rewarding to remember the things you do have. It’s amazing how harnessing the power of gratitude can transform your life and career. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, &lt;strong&gt;your attitude and outlook must also be backed up by your actions.&lt;/strong&gt; Another piece of advice Barbara gave me was to offer value to my clients. Since she told me this, I’ve made it the main mission of my business, and I can’t recommend highly enough that all of you do the same. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The work it takes to offer this value is often difficult and will require you to go above and beyond, but &lt;strong&gt;this short-term effort is well worth the long-term results.&lt;/strong&gt; If you follow this advice, your business is sure to thrive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Harnessing the power of gratitude can transform your life and career.%20Realestatecareersinalbany.com/harness-the-power-of-gratitude-and-watch-your-career-transform.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Harnessing the power of gratitude can transform your life and career.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But what about the specifics? What actions must you take to truly leverage the advice we’ve covered today? I’d like to invite you to learn more about this at my upcoming business planning event, where I’ll share proven techniques for establishing and running a successful real estate business. It costs just $49.99 to reserve your spot, but you can register for free when you use the code “VIP” at checkout. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eventbrite.com/e/3-hour-albany-real-estate-agent-business-planning-workshop-tickets-59073108257&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Click here to RVSP. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any other questions or would like more information, feel free to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 15:07:51 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>Realestatecareersinalbany.com/harness-the-power-of-gratitude-and-watch-your-career-transform.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">Realestatecareersinalbany.com/harness-the-power-of-gratitude-and-watch-your-career-transform.html</guid>
        
        <category>Events</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Our Business-Planning Seminar Has Everything You Need for Success</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/dgW9OX_i3aE?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;If your business has been struggling, our upcoming event can turn it all around.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The spring market’s here, and I hope you’re staying busy out there! It’s a great market, and if you’re not finding some great business, something is wrong. If you’ve found you’re unable to take advantage of these multiple-offer situations and new listings, we need to talk and figure out what you should be doing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Speaking of which, we have a great business-planning seminar coming up!&lt;/strong&gt; Join me at my office on April 30 to learn how to get a plan in place for growing your business and reaching a six-figure income. To sign up for this invaluable learning opportunity,&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eventbrite.com/e/3-hour-albany-real-estate-agent-business-planning-workshop-tickets-59073108257?utm_source=eb_email&amp;amp;utm_medium=email&amp;amp;utm_campaign=new_event_email&amp;amp;utm_term=viewmyevent_button&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; click this Eventbrite link.&lt;/a&gt; It’s only $49.95 to attend, but you can &lt;strong&gt;get in for free if you type in this code: VIP. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=This texting company works great, and agents should definitely have some sort of system in place.%20Realestatecareersinalbany.com/our-business-planning-seminar-has-everything-you-need-for-success.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“This texting company works great, and agents should definitely have some sort of system in place.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My own business is growing in a lot of ways as well, and things are going great for my team. Just the other day, I found a company that would reach out to my old leads. They started texting them, and within 15 minutes, I had 15 responses. &lt;strong&gt;Three of them were buyers who were ready to start the home search!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That came from the 150 leads I uploaded. &lt;strong&gt;I have 18,000 altogether.&lt;/strong&gt; Think about how much opportunity is still in that database, waiting to be turned into clients for my real estate business. This texting company works great, and agents should definitely have some sort of system in place. If this approach sounds interesting to you, I’d be more than happy to talk with you about it more and show you what’s working for our team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or would like more information about the event or my team’s processes, feel free to reach out to me. Until then, I look forward to seeing you at the seminar!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 09:11:32 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>Realestatecareersinalbany.com/our-business-planning-seminar-has-everything-you-need-for-success.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">Realestatecareersinalbany.com/our-business-planning-seminar-has-everything-you-need-for-success.html</guid>
        
        <category>Events</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The 2 Things That Set Me Apart</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/w-bcbWVrsN0?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;People always ask me what sets me apart, and I’m excited to share my answer with you now.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People always ask me, “What sets you apart?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These people typically expect my answer to focus on just one factor, but, personally, there are two traits that I believe are equally significant in what makes me unique. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I was named Times Union’s Best Real Estate Agent of the Year, I was literally working out of my bedroom doing 50 sales a year. Why, then, was I given this prestigious title? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It all comes down to the two traits I mentioned earlier, which I’ll list for you now: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. I have an airtight database marketing system.&lt;/strong&gt; Early on in my career, I learned to plug every single person I meet into my database right away. I also knew that simply entering names into a database wasn’t enough. Successful database marketing is all about putting meaningful systems in place for creating relationships and maintaining contact with each lead. Using video marketing, drip campaigns, and my tried-and-true CRM (Top Producer), I’ve built a proven system for success. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Knowledge is power, but it’s also wealth.%20Realestatecareersinalbany.com/the-2-things-that-set-me-apart.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Knowledge is power, but it’s also wealth.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. I commit myself to constant learning.&lt;/strong&gt; As a real estate professional, I’m always looking for educational opportunities. Wise people know how little they know. It’s okay not to know everything, so long as you’re always striving to know more. I devour audiobooks while I run, travel to attend conferences, and am always looking to connect with my fellow agents. Knowledge is power, but it’s also wealth. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These two things have really been at the core of my business. They drive everything I do, and they’ve been the foundation for my success from the very beginning. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that I’ve covered our main topic, I’d also like to share an exciting opportunity for you to earn $1,500. Here’s how: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My team is hiring. &lt;strong&gt;If you refer someone you know to me and I hire them, I’ll pay you $1,500 when they make their first sale.&lt;/strong&gt; It’s as simple as that. If you have anyone in mind, don’t hesitate to reach out to me with their name and number.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And, as always, if you have any other questions or would like more information, feel free to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 13:09:18 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>Realestatecareersinalbany.com/the-2-things-that-set-me-apart.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">Realestatecareersinalbany.com/the-2-things-that-set-me-apart.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Don’t Burn Bridges in Real Estate—Burn Boats</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/u8uj_nsmMSo?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;To succeed in this industry, you have to burn your boats. Let me tell you what that means.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In real estate, you don’t want to burn your bridges. However, you do want to burn your boats. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, I know I’ve burned bridges before in my career. I want to win clients and do my best for them, but my approach has sometimes been a bit too short-sighted. In real estate, though we compete with fellow agents, we often need to collaborate as well. Albany is small—you’re going to be doing business with agents more than once, &lt;strong&gt;so you simply can’t burn bridges.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 1519, Cortés invaded the island of Veracruz and burned his own army’s boats. They knew that they’d either win or die—&lt;strong&gt;there was no turning back.&lt;/strong&gt; Real estate is the same way: You have to make a commitment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=If you really want to find ultimate success in real estate, you need to commit to becoming a professional.%20Realestatecareersinalbany.com/dont-burn-bridges-in-real-estateburn-boats.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“If you really want to find ultimate success in real estate, you need to commit to becoming a professional.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was a top RE/MAX agent who had a great business in contracting and carpentry, but he decided to become a real estate agent. He could have simply dabbled in the industry, relying primarily on his previous trade while he built his real estate business. Instead, he sold his tools, made a full commitment, and became a top agent. &lt;strong&gt;That’s exactly what you need to do in real estate.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m afraid of heights, but I still went skydiving. I was terrified, but when I finally jumped out of the plane, I had made a commitment that there was no turning back from. &lt;strong&gt;And after making that commitment, I was at peace.&lt;/strong&gt; If you really want to find ultimate success in real estate, you need to commit to becoming a professional. We’re currently hiring, so if you’re ready to commit to your future in the industry, now’s your best chance to make it happen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re looking for a career in real estate with us, have any questions, or need further information, feel free to reach out to me. I look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 10:32:06 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>Realestatecareersinalbany.com/dont-burn-bridges-in-real-estateburn-boats.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">Realestatecareersinalbany.com/dont-burn-bridges-in-real-estateburn-boats.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why Do We Tend to Fail With Our Resolutions &amp; How Can This Be Fixed?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/9P1ZkDRs5xM?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;How are you faring with your New Year’s resolutions? Here’s how you can be sure you’ll have success with your goals for 2019, in real estate or otherwise.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re a month into 2019, which means it’s time to take initial stock of our New Year’s resolutions that we set for ourselves. Are yours still intact? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I came across a statistic recently that left me dumbfounded: &lt;strong&gt;92% of us will fail to live up to our resolutions by Valentine’s Day.&lt;/strong&gt; This obviously gave me pause—why do so many of us seem to fail in this way? We all have good intentions with our goals, whether they be in real estate, fitness, lifestyle, and so on. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What it boils down to is that &lt;strong&gt;we sometimes fail to rise to the level of our goals, and we, unfortunately, fall to the level of our systems and processes to get us to those goals.&lt;/strong&gt; Not having a system and process in place to accomplish any goal you set will inevitably lead to failure. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You know the old cliché: Successful people do what failures do not. This is partly true, but more importantly, &lt;strong&gt;successful people &lt;em&gt;consistently&lt;/em&gt; do what failures occasionally do. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a real estate sense, our office has more leads than we can handle, and all it takes is carving out two hours a day to pick up the phone and go after those leads. Following that approach is an easy, surefire way to sell 25 to 30 homes and make $100,000 a year.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Another key piece for hitting your goals is to take on some sort of identity.&lt;/strong&gt; I recently spoke to an ultramarathoner and in conversation with him, I mentioned that I’m a runner as well. This is the first time in my life that I’ve assumed the identity of being a runner. Having that identity fuels me to get out of bed to do my morning runs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Successful people consistently do what failures occasionally do.%20Realestatecareersinalbany.com/why-do-we-tend-to-fail-with-our-resolutions-how-can-this-be-fixed.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Successful people consistently do what failures occasionally do.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The same is true for you as a Realtor. &lt;strong&gt;You need to take on the identity that you’re a professional Realtor, money will flow into your life easily and often, and you’ll do what it takes to remain steadfast in that identity.&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions about goal attainment or the discipline and habits that go with it, please give me a call at 518-461-9937. I’d love to help in any way I can. Have an awesome 2019!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 15:53:47 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>Realestatecareersinalbany.com/why-do-we-tend-to-fail-with-our-resolutions-how-can-this-be-fixed.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">Realestatecareersinalbany.com/why-do-we-tend-to-fail-with-our-resolutions-how-can-this-be-fixed.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Share Your Wisdom and Become a Mentor</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/ixOY1P2oXzA?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Mentoring doesn’t just help others. It helps you as well.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2019’s here! I hope you had a great holiday season and are looking forward to making this year your best one yet. Though we’re hearing all sorts of news about how the real estate market will be heading downward, we can persevere; if you work hard and maintain the basics, you’re going to be successful in real estate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But today I want to focus on the one thing that could truly change your life this year: &lt;strong&gt;mentoring someone.&lt;/strong&gt; I’ve been blessed in becoming a mentor to a young man who needs guidance in his life. Helping him has actually helped me more than I ever thought possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you’re successful, it can be easy to forget about the rookies. &lt;strong&gt;Take someone in your office who’s struggling and help them.&lt;/strong&gt; Tell them how you handled your early years. You’ll not only instill wisdom upon those who need it, but you’ll also learn a lot about yourself and your own business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=By mentoring others, the life we save is often our own.%20Realestatecareersinalbany.com/share-your-wisdom-and-become-a-mentor.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“By mentoring others, the life we save is often our own.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In David Goggins’ book, “Can’t Hurt Me,” he talks about an instructor who trained two people on how to open a blocked airway. A few days later in a skydiving incident, the instructor’s airway became clogged and he was unable to breathe. &lt;strong&gt;He was then saved by the two people he had trained just two days prior.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By mentoring others, the life we save is often our own. So I challenge you to take someone under your wing; what you’re truly giving is much, much more than advice. &lt;strong&gt;And if you yourself are struggling, reach out to me, and I’ll pull you up.&lt;/strong&gt; I want you to be successful, and with the great business we have in Albany real estate, we can all afford to help one another grow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Contact me if you have any questions, have information, or simply need some help. I look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2019 09:13:30 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>Realestatecareersinalbany.com/share-your-wisdom-and-become-a-mentor.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">Realestatecareersinalbany.com/share-your-wisdom-and-become-a-mentor.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to Set Goals That Will Take Your Career to the Next Level in 2019</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/OWtNNYtsz2s?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;If you want to take your career to the next level in 2019, start by setting goals that seem impossible to you.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have you set your goals for 2019? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you haven’t already made a business plan for 2019, &lt;strong&gt;now’s the time to get your goals down in writing.&lt;/strong&gt; It’s a proven fact that if you write your goals down, you’ll have a better chance at achieving them. Even if you don’t achieve them, you will still accomplish more than what you would have if you didn’t write them down. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When setting your goals, you want to have a BHAG, or a “big, hairy, audacious goal.”&lt;/strong&gt; For example, what’s the highest number of homes you think you can sell? 75? Double it and shoot for 150. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I got my start in real estate, I was selling homes out of my bedroom. I had no systems, processes, or CRMs to speak of. My leads were sticky notes stuck to my laptop. Things have changed a lot since then, but that’s because I had the will to succeed. When I was in that bedroom, I set a goal to sell 100 homes in one year. At the time, I thought that was impossible, but I ended up selling 105 homes. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=You need to set a goal that’s so high that you might assume you can’t possibly do it.%20Realestatecareersinalbany.com/how-to-set-goals-that-will-take-your-career-to-the-next-level-in-2019.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“You need to set a goal that’s so high that you might assume you can’t possibly do it.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you set a crazy-high goal, you start thinking of the systems and processes you need to achieve that goal. This effect relates to an all-important principle about goals: &lt;strong&gt;It’s not achieving the goal that’s important—it’s about who you become while achieving that goal. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As you may know, I completed my very first marathon not too long ago, and you know what? It didn’t matter to me whether I finished that marathon or not. Obviously, I wanted to finish it, but it’s who I became during the three months of training leading up to that marathon that was really important. I lost 30 pounds, my resting heart rate dropped, and I just became a better person overall. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The same principle applies to real estate. You need to set a goal that’s so high that you might assume you can’t possibly do it. Just by setting it, you’ll still achieve more. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Look at it this way: If I set a goal to do 10 pushups, I’ll do 10 pushups and then quit. If I set a goal to do 100, though, I might just do 14, 16, or even 20 pushups. You might think you failed in achieving your goal if you do only 20 pushups, but you also doubled what you would’ve done if your goal was only 10 pushups. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, as you plan for 2019, remember to set your goals so high that you think there’s no way you’ll be able to achieve them. I promise that you’ll achieve amazing results. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re having trouble setting goals or you’d like to talk about what it’s like being on a team where you can make $100,000 a year, don’t hesitate to give me a call. I would absolutely love to help you reach your goals and have an amazing life and career. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As always, if you have any other questions for me or there’s anything else I can help you with, feel free to reach out to me as well. I look forward to speaking to you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 14:59:04 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>Realestatecareersinalbany.com/how-to-set-goals-that-will-take-your-career-to-the-next-level-in-2019.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">Realestatecareersinalbany.com/how-to-set-goals-that-will-take-your-career-to-the-next-level-in-2019.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>If You’re Serious About Your Real Estate Career, I Have an Offer for You</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Waz-iHEfb50?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Are you serious about your real estate career? If the answer is yes, I have an opportunity for you.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that the holidays are here, I have an opportunity to share with you and I want to talk a little about what’s happening in our industry. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Did you know that, in terms of the number of Realtors in our industry, we’re peaking? Over the next 18 to 24 months, though, &lt;strong&gt;we’re going to lose a lot of them as the market starts to shift.&lt;/strong&gt; That’s just an unfortunate part of the cycle our industry goes through.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the last month, I’ve had multiple people contact me looking for a job. The conversations I’ve had with them, though, usually involve them asking, “What can you offer me?” That’s the funny part about real estate—in what other industry would you call an employer and ask them what they can offer you? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=If you’re serious about your career, come talk to me.%20Realestatecareersinalbany.com/if-youre-serious-about-your-real-estate-career-i-have-an-offer-for-you.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“If you’re serious about your career, come talk to me.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last week, I interviewed someone who I knew within 30 seconds wouldn’t be a good fit for my company, but sure enough, the next day they told me they were considering taking the position. I had to remind them, of course, that I hadn’t even offered them the position yet. We’re a bit more selective than that when it comes to who we hire. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That being said, here’s my gift I want to offer you: If you’re serious about your career, come talk to me. I guarantee that if you’re hired, you will make at least $25,000 a year. If you don’t, I’ll personally write you a check for that amount. &lt;strong&gt;If you stick to our team’s regimen and follow our lead generation systems, you’ll not only make more money, but you’ll work fewer hours and have less stress. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, you need to be the right person for the job. There’s no barrier for entry into our business, and a lot of people get into thinking they’ll be driving a Mercedes 550 and making a few hundred grand a year without actually working. As we know, the reality is far different. &lt;strong&gt;Real estate is a great career, but it takes work.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re interested in this opportunity, don’t hesitate to give me a call or shoot me an email. I look forward to hearing from you, and I hope you have an absolutely fantastic holiday with your family.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;P.S. Our office is an unofficial drop-off site for Toys for Tots, so if you have any toys you’d like to donate this year, give them to us and we’ll make sure they find their way to this great organization.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2018 09:32:57 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>Realestatecareersinalbany.com/if-youre-serious-about-your-real-estate-career-i-have-an-offer-for-you.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">Realestatecareersinalbany.com/if-youre-serious-about-your-real-estate-career-i-have-an-offer-for-you.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Boost Your Own Success by Surrounding Yourself With People You Can Learn From</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/98kZ-L3PEx4?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Whether in life or business, surrounding yourself with people who are more successful than you is one of the biggest favors you can do for yourself.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The holidays can be a tough time for real estate, but don’t let that stop you from chasing success. There are a number of things you can do to stay successful no matter the state of the market, and one of the best ways is by &lt;strong&gt;surrounding yourself with greatness. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’d be surprised how big an impact the people in your life have on your success. In many ways, you are the average of the people you spend your time with. If you find the average income of your five closest friends, for example, chances are that figure will reflect your own current income. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So who are you hanging out with? If you’re always the smartest person in the room, then you’re doing something wrong. &lt;strong&gt;You should be surrounding yourself with people who are producing at a level you strive to someday reach—not at a level you’ve already surpassed. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And the same concept applies in life, too.  As you guys already know, I’m a runner. And as a runner, I often find that the people who motivate me most are the ones ahead of me in a race. It’s those kinds of people who push me to run faster. Even more interestingly, you never know when your own efforts will motivate someone else. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=If you’re always the smartest person in the room, then you’re doing something wrong.%20Realestatecareersinalbany.com/boost-your-own-success-by-surrounding-yourself-with-people-you-can-learn-from.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“If you’re always the smartest person in the room, then you’re doing something wrong.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take my most recent race, for example. I was keeping up a few paces behind this guy in front of me for most of the race, using his endurance as a way to keep myself going, only to find out by speaking to him later that he was using me as motivation too. He said that when he heard me coming up behind him, it made him want to run even faster. The point is this: &lt;strong&gt;Being around greatness makes you better.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So as the end of the year approaches, position yourself around people who you can learn and grow from. Find top producers and talk to them about what they’re doing to stay successful into 2019. Many of them will be happy to help you out. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any other questions or would like more information, feel free to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 13:47:48 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>Realestatecareersinalbany.com/boost-your-own-success-by-surrounding-yourself-with-people-you-can-learn-from.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">Realestatecareersinalbany.com/boost-your-own-success-by-surrounding-yourself-with-people-you-can-learn-from.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
