<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Albany Real Estate Careers and Training Video Blog with Kevin Clancy</title>
    <description>Kevin Clancy, a top Real Estate Agent in Albany, shares his own internal real estate agent training for free. His Real Estate Training, Tips and Advice will help you sell more homes in less time.</description>
    <link>http://Albanynyrealestateblog.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://Albanynyrealestateblog.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 14:28:50 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 14:28:50 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.2.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Jack of All Trades, Master of None: Why Not Try Being a Master of One?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/3HZkKWLfTU4?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you feel over-taxed in your real estate career and the results are not where you would like them to be, it might be time for you to refresh yourself with the basics and find one particular area to master.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looking to improve your real estate career? I’m here to help you make a smart decision when it comes to growing your business, improving your bottom line, and choosing a place to work in real estate sales. If you’d like to learn more about working with Clancy Real Estate, contact me at (518)861-7016 or Kevin@ClancyRealEstate.com.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today I want to impart some tips and insights that our team has learned over the years that you can use to save time and get to the income level that you deserve in your real estate career. We had some great one-on-one meetings this week, so I would like to share my takeaways with you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of my agents told me that he was making lots of calls but was not having any luck converting or reaching people on the phone. I asked him when he was making these calls, and he said he was making calls between 1:00 p.m. and 3:00 p.m because of other things in his life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are calling out in the early afternoon, you are wasting your time—you would be better off going to the gym or going out for a bike ride. The best time to call is between 6:00 p.m. and 8:00 p.m. at night, and between 8:00 a.m. and 10:00 a.m. in the morning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have an agent who time blocked those periods for calls and she was making $10,000 a month. Her connect ratio was so much higher than if she had made the calls in the early afternoon. &lt;strong&gt;Success can be manufactured by properly structuring your day, such as reevaluating your time blocks.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our team often feels like it is being pulled in 18 different directions—we are trying to door knock, work on our scripts, call FSBOs with Vulcan, write handwritten notes, check our emails, get sold leads, and figure out new ways to succeed in real estate without working.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My takeaway from my agents was that we were not focusing on the basics. While trying to juggle all these tasks, we were unable to do any of them exceptionally well. On this, I agree with the genius Gary Keller: &lt;strong&gt;You want to focus on one thing at a time.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Years ago in coaching, a friend of mine was struggling on the verge of bankruptcy in his business. I told him that he needed to &lt;strong&gt;focus on the fundamentals.&lt;/strong&gt; He was trying to implement too many things at the same time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=WHILE TRYING TO JUGGLE ALL THESE TASKS, WE WERE UNABLE TO DO ANY OF THEM EXCEPTIONALLY WELL.%20http://Albanynyrealestateblog.com/dont-try-to-be-jack-of-all-trades.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“WHILE TRYING TO JUGGLE ALL THESE TASKS, WE WERE UNABLE TO DO ANY OF THEM EXCEPTIONALLY WELL.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Find your one weak area that, with improvement and mastery, will get your business where you want it to be. It could be mastering scripts or market knowledge. &lt;strong&gt;You will not master anything if you are trying to do 18 things at once.&lt;/strong&gt; After meeting with many teams over the years, I’ve seen that top agents all master one area. That doesn’t mean you need to limit yourself, however. You can continue improving other areas after you’ve mastered one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to know what it’s like to be on a team and have the career and life you deserve, reach out to me. Here is to your continued success in real estate!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 09:54:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://Albanynyrealestateblog.com/dont-try-to-be-jack-of-all-trades.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://Albanynyrealestateblog.com/dont-try-to-be-jack-of-all-trades.html</guid>
        
        <category>Albany Real estate coaching</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What Are the Keys to Success in Real Estate?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/xog-8Hec_0g?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can’t find success in real estate on your own. You need to learn from others and apply that to your own career. Here’s how I can help you do that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looking to improve your real estate career? I’m here to help you make a smart decision when it comes to growing your business, improving your bottom line, and choosing a place to work in real estate sales. If you’d like to learn more about working with Clancy Real Estate, contact me at (518)861-7016 or Kevin@ClancyRealEstate.com.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m back to share some more ideas and insights that I’ve gathered in my 25+ years in the business. I’m heading down to meet with some top agents in the next week which got me thinking about the keys to success.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why do I travel to so many conferences like this? &lt;strong&gt;Because I want to surround myself with greatness.&lt;/strong&gt; I like being in places where I’m not the smartest guy in the room. You need to surround yourself with successful people too. It will help you start thinking bigger.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have an obligation to succeed. &lt;strong&gt;To yourself, to your family, and to the ones you love.&lt;/strong&gt; Teddy Roosevelt once said, “Comparison is the thief of joy.” However, it also works in reverse. If you’re in an office with average agents who sell five or six homes per year, you might be feeling really great if you have sold eight homes, but you shouldn’t.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My team sold 300 homes last year, but we stink. You know why? 6,000 homes were sold in the capital region last year. &lt;strong&gt;Our market share is so small and there is so much opportunity for us.&lt;/strong&gt; The abundance of business is amazing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re not happy where you are in your career, give me a call. I’d be happy to go out for coffee, have a sit-down, and show you the path to true success in this industry. My goal in life is to grow people, and I’d love to do the same with you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s more business out there for everyone, so that’s why I’m offering you this opportunity. &lt;strong&gt;If you’re interested in going to Mike Ferry’s superstar retreat for free, give me a call and I’ve got a free ticket for you.&lt;/strong&gt; Mike is one of the best minds in real estate and this will absolutely change your life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=IF YOU’RE INTERESTED IN GOING TO MIKE FERRY’S SUPERSTAR RETREAT FOR FREE, GIVE ME A CALL TODAY.%20http://Albanynyrealestateblog.com/i-want-to-share-keys-to-success-with-you.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“IF YOU’RE INTERESTED IN GOING TO MIKE FERRY’S SUPERSTAR RETREAT FOR FREE, GIVE ME A CALL TODAY.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any other questions, don’t hesitate to give me a call or send me an email. I would love to hear from you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 13:29:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://Albanynyrealestateblog.com/i-want-to-share-keys-to-success-with-you.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://Albanynyrealestateblog.com/i-want-to-share-keys-to-success-with-you.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate Coaching</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How Are You Creating Value?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/cbs33gaa8ik?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re willing to deliver more value to your client than what you’re paid for, your career in real estate will take off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looking to improve your real estate career? I’m here to help you make a smart decision when it comes to growing your business, improving your bottom line, and choosing a place to work in real estate sales. If you’d like to learn more about working with Clancy Real Estate, contact me at (518)861-7016 or Kevin@ClancyRealEstate.com.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been traveling and attending a lot of conferences lately and learning a lot from them. One of those conferences was Mike Ferry’s, and he talked about today’s topic: creating more value than what you’re paid for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t think any business coach will tell you that creating more value than what you’re paid for is a bad business model. However, most companies provide as little service as possible to their clients in order to get paid. In the long run, I believe this can cost you far more in terms of referrals, goodwill, and your reputation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How can you as a Realtor provide massive value to your clients? Go the extra mile. &lt;strong&gt;Do more than what other agents do during the transaction.&lt;/strong&gt; I experienced a couple examples of this outside the real estate world recently.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first was an Uber ride. My driver had the interior of his car decked out with LED lights, he had bottled water available, and he even asked me what kind of music I wanted to listen to. It was exceptional service compared to the average Uber or cab ride. This guy’s attitude was phenomenal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second was when my car had a flat tire and I had to call AAA. The kid they sent out to me had a positive attitude and didn’t complain, and I ended up tipping him very well even though I didn’t have to. He did such a great job, was such a great guy, and gave me such a positive experience that I felt obligated to tip him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=ALWAYS GO THE EXTRA MILE FOR YOUR CLIENTS.%20http://Albanynyrealestateblog.com/how-are-you-creating-value.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“ALWAYS GO THE EXTRA MILE FOR YOUR CLIENTS.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Real estate works the same way. All the way from the start of the transaction to the closing gift, &lt;strong&gt;it’s important how your client perceives you.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaking of closing gifts, if you need an idea for one, our team has started using personalized engraved cutting boards. You can see an example of one in the video above. The point is, it’s the thought that counts. Put some thought into what you give your client. Give them something they can use and something that will remind them of you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you’re willing to deliver more value to your client than what you’re paid for, I guarantee your career in real estate will take off.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As always, if you’re not where you want to be in your real estate career, give me a call and I’d be happy to sit down and talk to you about how I generate leads. If you have any other questions, feel free to reach out to me as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s to your continued success in real estate.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 12:24:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://Albanynyrealestateblog.com/how-are-you-creating-value.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://Albanynyrealestateblog.com/how-are-you-creating-value.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Importance of Holding Yourself Accountable</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Y4vLpM-LS2g?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re not holding yourself accountable in your business, you need to find someone to do it for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looking to improve your real estate career? I’m here to help you make a smart decision when it comes to growing your business, improving your bottom line, and choosing a place to work in real estate sales. If you’d like to learn more about working with Clancy Real Estate, contact me at (518)861-7016 or Kevin@ClancyRealEstate.com.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Who holds you accountable in your business?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a question that was posed to me recently by a real estate coach, and it’s an interesting one because right now is the first time I haven’t had a real estate coach in eight or 10 years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Us Realtors hire coaches to hold us accountable for tasks we need to complete each week. Otherwise, there’s no accountability in our business—there’s no one telling you to get out of bed, get to the office, and get things done. In real estate, you’re an independent contractor. If you want to sleep in until 10 a.m. every day, you can do so (you probably won’t be in the business very long though).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was listening to the audiobook version of “The 5 Second Rule” recently, and the book’s premise is that you have five seconds to act on something, and &lt;strong&gt;your role is to be a parent to yourself.&lt;/strong&gt; A parent’s role is to help their children grow and excel, but their role is also to get them to do things they generally won’t do on their own, so being a parent to yourself is what accountability is all about.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=IT’S IMPORTANT IN THIS BUSINESS TO STAY ON TRACK AND HAVE AN ACCOUNTABILITY PARTNER.%20http://Albanynyrealestateblog.com/the-importance-of-accountability-in-our.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“IT’S IMPORTANT IN THIS BUSINESS TO STAY ON TRACK AND HAVE AN ACCOUNTABILITY PARTNER.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This week, think about who holds you accountable. &lt;strong&gt;If you’re not holding yourself accountable and you’re not self-motivated, get an accountability partner.&lt;/strong&gt; On our team, everybody has an accountability partner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you need help being accountable, call me and I would be happy to use our systems and processes to hold you accountable and get your career on track. Otherwise, call a real estate coach.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any other questions or you’re interested in joining our team, don’t hesitate to reach out to me. I look forward to hearing from you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 10:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://Albanynyrealestateblog.com/the-importance-of-accountability-in-our.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://Albanynyrealestateblog.com/the-importance-of-accountability-in-our.html</guid>
        
        <category>Albany Real estate coaching</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What Is the Biggest Thing Holding You Back?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/hT_kWpOlZ20?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is driving your success, and what’s holding you back? These are questions I’ll address today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looking to improve your real estate career? I’m here to help you make a smart decision when it comes to growing your business, improving your bottom line, and choosing a place to work in real estate sales. If you’d like to learn more about working with Clancy Real Estate, contact me at (518)861-7016 or Kevin@ClancyRealEstate.com.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This week, I found some inspiration from an unexpected source. I was watching a video featuring Will Smith, and this video actually reminded me of why I am where I’m at today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Will Smith has always been a hero of mine. When he talks about his career, he often talks about the fear of not knowing where his work will lead him next. Even though he would never have to work another day in his life if he didn’t want to, he genuinely cares about what he does.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think a lot of successful people have this same concern and this same drive. A lot of successful people work from fear, and this is definitely the case for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If I’m not doing deals, I’m not going to produce income. So, the question this brings up is: What drives your success?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All of us have a desire to succeed, but many of us lack discipline. This lack of discipline is what really kills our businesses. &lt;strong&gt;You can talk all you want about the things you want, but all that talk will lead you nowhere if you don’t act on it.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=YOU HAVE TO PUT IN THE WORK TO GET THE SUCCESS YOU WANT.%20http://Albanynyrealestateblog.com/whats-holding-you-back-from-success.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“YOU HAVE TO PUT IN THE WORK TO GET THE SUCCESS YOU WANT.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As real estate professionals, we all want to be great at what we do. But being great is a lot of work. It requires us to train hard, work on scripts, make calls, and be persistent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During my recent training session with Mike Ferry, he brought an agent up on stage who sold 100 homes and had 150 listings this year. He made 30 contacts a day, which is 150 contacts a week. This is approximately 59,000 contacts a year. This means to get 150 listings, he failed 58,050 times. Still, this guy had a great year—he earned $400,000, all because he was willing to “walk the walk.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, are you willing to do so, too? Are you willing to act on the goals you talk about and make them happen? I think the answer for many of us is no, and that is fine. But, realize that you won’t be able to find the success you want if you don’t have the discipline to do what it takes. &lt;strong&gt;The biggest thing holding us back from success is our inability to do things that we’d rather not do.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The question to consider is, “How badly do you want success?” Life is a series of actions and reactions. You have to put in the work to get the success you want.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, I’d like to share a video with you that I saw myself for the first time about six or seven years ago. The video is called “The Strangest Secret,” and it talks about many of the same things we’ve gone over today, and I absolutely recommend checking it out. I can almost guarantee it will change your life, because it definitely changed mine. You can find that video here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any other questions, would like more information, or are curious about joining a team and making six figures, feel free to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2018 12:12:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://Albanynyrealestateblog.com/whats-holding-you-back-from-success.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://Albanynyrealestateblog.com/whats-holding-you-back-from-success.html</guid>
        
        <category>Motivation</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What Separates a Mediocre Agent From a Top Producer?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/IXaBbFcaV-8?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mindset is what separates mediocre agents from top-producing agents—mediocre agents have static mindsets, while top producers have growth mindsets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looking to improve your real estate career? I’m here to help you make a smart decision when it comes to growing your business, improving your bottom line, and choosing a place to work in real estate sales. If you’d like to learn more about working with Clancy Real Estate, contact me at (518)861-7016 or Kevin@ClancyRealEstate.com.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What separates a mediocre agent from a top producer?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve worked with dozens of agents over the years who came to our team making $15,000 or $20,000 a year and worked their way up to making $200,000+ a year, and there are many possible answers to this question. You could say things like knowledge, drive, talent, or motivation, but it’s actually none of those traits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It’s their mindset—that’s what separates a mediocre agent from a top-producing agent.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve come to the realization that there are two types of mindsets: a static mindset and a growth mindset. An agent with a static mindset is one who isn’t reading books or putting the time in to grow as a person. They want to be told they’re great, they don’t want criticism, and they don’t want to grow. An agent with a growth mindset is the exact opposite. They thrive on learning. They watch videos, read books, and devour information to make them better. They embrace criticism because they know it makes them better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me give you an example of a growth mindset. I got my butt kicked this week on a listing appointment. It was a great listing, and I wanted it badly, but I lost it to another firm. That kind of thing happens—you’re not going to win every listing. Early in my career, I would’ve gotten upset about something like that. In this case, though, I called the seller, congratulated them on picking a great agent, and asked them why they didn’t pick us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was kind of funny—they said our firm was too big. I always think of us as a small firm, and at this listing presentation I was explaining how we could compete with some of the bigger national firms. Yet, I wasn’t really in tune with what the seller wanted, which was a smaller firm with a more personalized experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Had I not asked the seller why they didn’t choose us and received their feedback, I wouldn’t have been able to improve. Now I know if I’m on my next listing appointment and I sense that someone wants more personalized service, I should stress how we really are a smaller firm with personal service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=ARE YOU A GROWTH-MINDED PERSON OR A STATIC-MINDED PERSON?%20http://Albanynyrealestateblog.com/the-difference-between-mediocre-agents.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“ARE YOU A GROWTH-MINDED PERSON OR A STATIC-MINDED PERSON?”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A person with a static mindset would never get that far or try to improve or grow. They’d continue to lose listings and never change their listing presentation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The question now becomes, if you’re having a bad day, how do you change? We all do different things. I’m about to go for a run this afternoon to clear my mind and work on some things I want to work on during that time. I suggest you take some time out of your day to clear your mind and focus on what you want to do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This week, think about two things—whether you’re a growth-mindset person or a static-mindset person.&lt;/strong&gt; Are you constantly growing and do you want to be the best agent you can be or is real estate just something you plod along at?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want something to help you with your career, I have tens of thousands of dollars worth of books, tapes, and other material that can help you with your career that I’d be happy to share with you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any more questions about this topic or you want to know what it’s like on our team, don’t hesitate to reach out to me. We’re still looking for one agent who wants to earn six figures a year with all leads provided. Have an awesome week, and I look forward to hearing from you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 12:43:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://Albanynyrealestateblog.com/the-difference-between-mediocre-agents.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://Albanynyrealestateblog.com/the-difference-between-mediocre-agents.html</guid>
        
        <category>Kevin Clancy Real Estate Training</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Would You Like to Take Your Career to the Next Level?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/liQ9DQOP0_Y?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m on the lookout for a new agent to join my team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looking to improve your real estate career? I’m here to help you make a smart decision when it comes to growing your business, improving your bottom line, and choosing a place to work in real estate sales. If you’d like to learn more about working with Clancy Real Estate, contact me at (518)861-7016 or Kevin@ClancyRealEstate.com.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Right now, I’m looking for a highly qualified, full-time real estate agent with a minimum of two years of experience to join my team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On average, I receive 200 to 300 buyer leads per month, and I need your help to handle the surplus of buyers calling my office daily. &lt;strong&gt;I want to help you take your career to the next level and focus on what you do best, which is selling homes.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=IF YOU DON’T MAKE $75,000 IN YOUR FIRST YEAR, I’LL PAY YOU THE DIFFERENCE.%20http://Albanynyrealestateblog.com/a-new-career-opportunity-is-waiting-for.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“IF YOU DON’T MAKE $75,000 IN YOUR FIRST YEAR, I’LL PAY YOU THE DIFFERENCE.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As one of the top real estate agents in Albany, I can guarantee that you’ll make $75,000 in your first year or I’ll pay you the difference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Join me, the Capital Region’s No. 1 real estate agent as voted by the readers of The Times Union, and the only agent that real estate mogul and “Shark Tank” star Barbara Corcoran recommends in Albany.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re interested in applying or you have any other questions, give me a call or message me here on our website. I look forward to hearing from you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 12:35:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://Albanynyrealestateblog.com/a-new-career-opportunity-is-waiting-for.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://Albanynyrealestateblog.com/a-new-career-opportunity-is-waiting-for.html</guid>
        
        <category>Kevin Clancy Real Estate Coaching</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An Opportunity to Further Your Career and Help the Community</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Jo6rNv--1oQ?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Are you interested in serving your community? If so, there are two opportunities I’d like to go over with you today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looking to improve your real estate career? I’m here to help you make a smart decision when it comes to growing your business, improving your bottom line, and choosing a place to work in real estate sales. If you’d like to learn more about working with Clancy Real Estate, contact me at (518)861-7016 or Kevin@ClancyRealEstate.com.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before I get into today’s main topic, I’ve got a huge opportunity for you. My company is always doing everything we can to give back to the community that gives us so much, and right now we’re looking for two agents to join us in doing so. &lt;strong&gt;If you want to make six figures and work on a team with a culture that values both hard work and having fun, please give me a call.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m offering a $1,000 bonus to you or someone you know who is interested in joining our team. This bonus will become available as soon as you close your first transaction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=MY COMPANY IS ALWAYS DOING EVERYTHING WE CAN TO GIVE BACK TO THE COMMUNITY THAT GIVES US SO MUCH.%20http://Albanynyrealestateblog.com/you-can-help-us-give-back.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“MY COMPANY IS ALWAYS DOING EVERYTHING WE CAN TO GIVE BACK TO THE COMMUNITY THAT GIVES US SO MUCH.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, let’s move onto the main subject. There is an event put on by the St. Baldrick’s Foundation, a private charity and childhood cancer research foundation, coming up March 11 at the Westmere Fire Department. &lt;strong&gt;You can see a video message from St. Baldricks at the 2:45 mark in the video above.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is an event my team and I have been happy to support every year. Also, if you or someone you refer to us join our team, we will personally donate $2,000 to St. Baldrick’s after you close your first transaction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any other questions or would like more information, feel free to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 10:15:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://Albanynyrealestateblog.com/you-can-help-us-give-back.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://Albanynyrealestateblog.com/you-can-help-us-give-back.html</guid>
        
        <category>Kevin Clancy real estate coaching</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How Can You Increase Your Income in Real Estate?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/7GhZYulxYGA?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How can you increase the amount of money you make in the real estate industry? I have three key ways you can do just that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looking to improve your real estate career? I’m here to help you make a smart decision when it comes to growing your business, improving your bottom line, and choosing a place to work in real estate sales. If you’d like to learn more about working with Clancy Real Estate, contact me at (518)861-7016 or Kevin@ClancyRealEstate.com.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that it’s 2018, I hope that you’re looking forward to growing your business and increasing your income. If you are, the question becomes “How can you increase your income?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=PEOPLE WILL WANT TO PAY YOU MORE IF THEY ASSOCIATE YOUR BRAND AND REPUTATION WITH THE QUALITY OF THE SERVICE THAT YOU BRING.%20http://Albanynyrealestateblog.com/how-to-make-more-money-in-real-estate.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“PEOPLE WILL WANT TO PAY YOU MORE IF THEY ASSOCIATE YOUR BRAND AND REPUTATION WITH THE QUALITY OF THE SERVICE THAT YOU BRING.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are major three ways you can increase the amount of money you make in real estate:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. You can sell more houses.&lt;/strong&gt; Everyone likes to brag about how many homes they’ve sold. That’s great, but I’d rather sell fewer homes at a higher price than more homes at a lower price. It’s less stress on my staff, less work in general, and we’re still making the same amount of money. You can focus on selling more homes, but it’s a tremendous amount of work, and it’s probably the hardest of these three options to carry out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. You can sell higher-priced homes.&lt;/strong&gt; Let’s assume that you’re selling below the average sales price in your area; how can you increase your personal average sales price? I recently spoke with a top-producing KW agent who moved her average price point up to $1 million. She said that doing it was easy; she bought a $1 million house, joined a country club, and started hanging out with people who also lived in a millionaire community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. That’s not achievable for everyone, however.&lt;/strong&gt; You just have to make a conscious effort to determine what sort of price point you’re willing to work with and what your bottom cutoff level is. Sticking to the lower levels, unfortunately, means that you’re not maximizing your dollar return for the price point you’re working in. We’re creating a separate division for low-end properties with a team dedicated to working with them so that high-end properties won’t reject listing with us, thinking that we’re only for low-end clients.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can obtain a higher marketing fee. Your marketing fee only becomes an issue in the absence of value. If you’re not creating value for your client, the price you ask for will be contested. It’s like the difference between paying more for a brand name product instead of paying less for an off-brand product. People will want to pay you more if they associate your brand and reputation with the quality of the service that you bring.
Lastly, another way to make more money is to join a better team. I have two spots open on my team, but they’re only for agents who want to make six figures. We have a great team, I’m providing all the leads, and we have a lot of fun with what we do. If you have any questions about what you can do to earn more money in the real estate industry or would like to know about joining the team, feel free to reach out. I’d love to speak with you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 16:22:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://Albanynyrealestateblog.com/how-to-make-more-money-in-real-estate.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://Albanynyrealestateblog.com/how-to-make-more-money-in-real-estate.html</guid>
        
        <category>Kevin Clancy Real Estate Training</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Whats Your 2018 Marketing Budget?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/umc2o07_Dzw?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why did I spend $400,000 on marketing in 2017? For starters, I got a great return.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looking to improve your real estate career? I’m here to help you make a smart decision when it comes to growing your business, improving your bottom line, and choosing a place to work in real estate sales. If you’d like to learn more about working with Clancy Real Estate, contact me at (518)861-7016 or Kevin@ClancyRealEstate.com.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2018 is here and we’re off to a great start. Before we get too far into the new year, I wanted to make sure I talked to you about your marketing budget and what your plans are for it this year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I spent over $400,000 last year on marketing.&lt;/strong&gt; That might sound crazy, but when you see that my return was 4:1 at around $1.6 million, it doesn’t seem so crazy after all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I track all of our spending on different marketing avenues. We’re always on the cutting edge and trying to use innovative techniques to get more business. One way we’re doing this is through a partnership with Regal Cinemas. Not only do our ads come up on the screens before movies, they also pop up on people’s phones in the theatre via a geolocation feature. &lt;strong&gt;I can then track all my deals from this section of the budget.&lt;/strong&gt; When I can say that I spend “X” amount and brought in “Y” amount of money because of it, then my marketing makes sense from a profitability standpoint. Then it’s easy when it comes time to decide where to re-invest. I already know the places that have given me the best return, so I can go to them first.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=I TRACK ALL OF OUR MARKETING SPENDING.%20http://Albanynyrealestateblog.com/whats-your-marketing-budget.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“I TRACK ALL OF OUR MARKETING SPENDING.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you don’t think you have a marketing budget, think again. Even if you’re just starting out, sending emails and making phone calls and sending thank you notes will barely cost you a thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2018 is here and we’re excited for what the year has to bring.&lt;/strong&gt; If you want to learn more about where we spend our money when it comes to marketing or where you should be spending in order to maximize your return on investment, don’t hesitate to reach out and give me a call or send me an email. I’d be happy to talk on the phone or meet up for a cup of coffee. I look forward to hearing from you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2018 11:58:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://Albanynyrealestateblog.com/whats-your-marketing-budget.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://Albanynyrealestateblog.com/whats-your-marketing-budget.html</guid>
        
        <category>Kevin Clancy real estate coaching</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
